Guide to the Myron Gustin Fincher Papers, 1908-1993
Fincher, Myron Gustin papers, 1908-1993
- Series V: Food and Drug Administration Files
  - Valsyn Gel, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Drug Summaries, ca. 1967-1971 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous, ca. 1967-1971 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Series VI: Writings and Speeches
  - "Bang Abortion Disease or Abortion, 1930 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - "Care, Management and Breeding Problems in the Mare," Cornell Annual Conference for Veterinarians, January 4, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Reminiscences, September 14, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - "History of Veterinary Medicine", December 8,1967 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - "Hoge Poge of Comments," Kansas State, February 27, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - "How to Handle Cows that are Non-Breeders" (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - "Jurisprudence Talk at Cornell University", May 23,1969 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Nigeria - General, 1965-1967, n.d. (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Nigeria - "Livestock Problems in Nigeria," Modern Veterinary Practice, February 1968 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - "Remarks on Sterility in Cattle", 1927 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Talks to Boys and Girls, Greece, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Veterinary Education, January 8, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - "Veterinary Medicine in Italy, February 15 - July 5, 1973," FDA, November 15, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous, ca. 1950-1980 (Box 33, Folder 45)
- Series VII. Veterinary Ephemera
  - Cattle Catalogs, ca. 1950-1970 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - French Journals, 1951-1953 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Professional Organizations, ca. 1945-1970 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Horses, ca. 1950-1970 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Advertisements, ca. 1940-1970 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - New York State, ca. 1940-1960 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - 20th World Veterinary Congress, Thessaloniki, July 6-12, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous, ca. 1940-1965 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - Reprint Lists (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Scrapbook - folder 1, 1944-1950 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Scrapbook - folder 2, 1944-1950 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - Borden Award Presented to Myron Fincher by the American Veterinary Medical Association, 1954-08 (Box 35)
- Series VIII. Cornell Office Files
  - S.D. Johnson's Correspondence
    - A, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - B, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - C, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - D, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - E, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - F, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - G, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - H, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - I-J, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - K, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - L, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - M, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Mc, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - N, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - O, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - P, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Q-R, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - S, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - T, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - U-V, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - W, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - XYZ, 1939-1940 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 1937
    - A-I, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - J-P, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - R-Z, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 1937-1938
    - A-B, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - C-G, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - H-M, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - N-S, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - T-W, 1937-1938 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - 1942-1943
    - A, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Army, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - B, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - B, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Bruce, Ronald (Meridale Farms), 1940-1943 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - C, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Conference Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - D, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - E, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - F, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Faulder, E.T., 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Faber, Robert, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - G, 1941-1943 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - G, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Gadd, John D., 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - H, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - H, 1941-1943 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Hagan, William A., 1941-1943 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - I, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - J, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - K, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Kent, L.C. (College Financial Secretary), 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - L, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - L, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - M, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - M, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Mc, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - N, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - O, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - P, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Q-R, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - S, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - S, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - T, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - U-V, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - W-Z, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 1944
    - A-B, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - C, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - D, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - E-F, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - G, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - H, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - H-I, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - J, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1945
    - A, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - B, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - C-D, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - E-G, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - H, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - J, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous reports and papers, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - 1945-1946
    - A, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - B, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - B, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - C, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - D, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - D, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Dean's Office, 1944-1946 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - E, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Executive Board for the NYS Veterinary Medical Society, 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - F, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - G, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - G, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - H, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - H, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Howe, Ivan G., 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - I-J, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - K, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - King Ranch [Original photographs in Veterinary Photograph Collection], 1946 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - L, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Leonard, Edwin-Tully Meeting, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - M, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - M, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Mastitis Program-Applicant positions, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Mastitis Program, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Mastitis Program-O.W. Schalm Articles, 1941-1946 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - N, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - New York State Veterinary Medical Society, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - O, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - P, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - R, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Refresher course, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - New York Farm Radio News, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - S, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - S, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - S, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Scheidy Report, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - T, 1945-1946 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - U, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - V, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - W, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - W, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1946-1947
    - A, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Ambulatory Clinic, 1942-1946 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Ambulatory Clinic, 1943-1945 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1945-1947 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - B, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - B, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Bree, Ronald-Meridale Farms, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Bree, Ronald-Meridale Farms, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - C, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Conference Program, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - D, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - E, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - F, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - G, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - G.L.F. Grant, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Green, D.F. Merck & Co, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - H, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - H, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Hagan, W.A., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Hagan, W.A., 1947-1949 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Hodges, H.G., 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Hopson, George-Public Relations Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - J, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Johnson, S.D., 1945 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - K, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Kent, L.C., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - L, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - M, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Mc, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Medicine Department, 1946-1948 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1946-1948 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Milliman, T.E., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous material, ca. 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - N, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - O, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - P, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Penicillin, 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Peet, Nelson R., 1946 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Pitman-Moore Company, 1945-1947 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - R, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Regan, J.J., 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Radio, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - S, 1946-1947 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - S, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - T, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Students, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Skeffington, L.B., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - State Herds, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - N.Y.S. Veterinary Medical Society, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Sterility, 1944-1946 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Streptomycin, ca. 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - U, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - V-W, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Winters, Asa A., 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - XYZ, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - "X" Disease, ca. 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Canton, NY, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Mastitis Control Program-Monthly reports, Canton, NY, 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - College Dairy Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Ambulatory Clinic, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous material, ca. 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 1947-1948
    - Bly, H.J.-Canton Lab, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - A, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Applications, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Automobile reports, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - B, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - C, 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Artificial insemination, ca. 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - A, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - American Society for the Study of Sterility, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Artificial Breeding, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - B, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1945-1948 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - C, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - D, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - E, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - F, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - G, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Gannett Farms, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - G.L.F. Grants, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Graduate School, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Green, David F., 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Gumaer, K.I., 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - H, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Hagan, W.A., 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Hagan, W.A., 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Hopson, George, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Hodges, H.G., 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Howe, Ivan G., 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - I, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - J, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Jenson-Salsbery Lab, 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Meetings, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - K, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - King's State Park, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Kent, L.C.-Mastitis Control Program, 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - L, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Lederle Laboratories Division, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - M, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Mc, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1942-1948 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Milking Machine care, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - N, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - O, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Veterinary Ophthalmology, ca. 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - 1948
    - A, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Anticipated work, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - B, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Barn Management, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Bierly, Ivan R., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Budget Reports, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - C, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Canton Laboratories, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Child, Robert B.-Rural Radio Network, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - County Agent List, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - County Extension Work Programs, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Crowe, C.F., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - D, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Barn Management Letter, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Dairy Industry Department, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Dairymen's League Contest, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - E, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Environment Analysis Newsclippings, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Earlville, NY Mastitis Laboratory-opening, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Earlville Laboratory, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - East Aurora Laboratory, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Entomology Department, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Extension Service, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - F, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Farmingdale Laboratory, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Farmingdale Laboratory, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Farm Bureau, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Field Veterinarians, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - G, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Gannett Farms Letter, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - General Electric-W.G. Givens, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - H, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Dr. Hileboe's Speech-January Conference, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Hagan, W.A., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Hopson, G.H., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Ithaca's Mastitis Program's Monthly Reports, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - J, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - K, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Kingston Laboratory-Monthly Reports, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Kingston Laboratory, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Kingston Laboratory, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Kent, L.C., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - L, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - M, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous mastitis material, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Mastitis Program papers, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Milking machines, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Milk quality, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Mastitis surveys, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Mastitis monthly reports, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Summary reports of mastitis program, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Monroe, B.W., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - P, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Plimpton, S.J., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Pitman-Moore Co., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Policy Committee, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Q-R, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Reed, F.I.-East Aurora Laboratory, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Regan, J.J., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - S, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Schenley Laboratories, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Sharp and Dohme, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - E.R. Squibb & Sons, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - State Herds, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Stone, W.S.-NYS Veterinary Medical Society, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - T, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Tucker, E.W.-Kingston Laboratory, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - U, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - V, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - W, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - XYZ, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - 1948-1949
    - A, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report, 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Aureomycin, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - American Society for the Study of Sterility, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Artificial Insemination, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - B, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Budget Plans for 1948, ca. 1947 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Bill of Rights, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - C, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - CIBA Laboratories, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - D, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Dewey Herd, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - E, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Expense Accounts, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - F, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Farm and Home Week, 1943-1948 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Forest Farms, 1941-1946 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Forest Farms, 1943-1948 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - G, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Gannett Farms, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - H, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Hagan, W.A.-Report, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Hagan, W.A.-NYS Veterinary College, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Higley, P.I., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Hodges, H.G., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Howe, Ivan G., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - I-J, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - K, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Kent, L.C., 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Kent, L.C.-Medicine Department, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Kent, L.C., 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - L, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - M, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Mastitis-New Projects, 1946-1950 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Mastitis Laboratories, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Canton Laboratory-Mastitis Control Program, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Earlville Regional Mastitis Lab, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - East Aurora Regional Mastitis Lab, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Farmingdale Regional Mastitis Lab, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Kingston Regional Mastitis Lab, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Milking machines, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Menotti, A.R., 1949 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Murphy, J.M., 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - N, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - O, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - P, 1948-1949 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Panel Discussion at NYS Veterinary Medical Society Meeting, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Papers, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Pen Stabling, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Policy Committee, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Public Relations, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Published material, 1946, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Publicity Kit for State Veterinary Medical Conventions, ca. 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Q-R, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Radio Talks, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Research Projects, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Regan, J.J., 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - S, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - S, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Copies of stencils, ca. 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Sharp & Dohme, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Student Faculty Seminar, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Schenley Labs, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - E.R. Squibb & Sons, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - NYS Veterinary Medical Society, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - T, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - U, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - University Testing Service, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - V, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Vacation Information, 1947 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Veterinarians Committee on Mastitis Program, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - W, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Wallace Labs, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - XYZ, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - 1949
    - B, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Bang's Disease, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Beacon Milling Company, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Boardman, Donald A., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Bristol Laboratories Inc., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Bureau of Animal Industry, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - B.A.I.-D.B.H. Dalrymple, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - B.A.I.-I. G. Howe, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - B.A.I.-E.V. Moore, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - B.A.I.-W.S. Stone, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - C, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - D, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Day, Edmund E., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Delaval Separator Company, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - E, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - F, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - G, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - H, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Hagan, W.A., 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Hagan, W.A., 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Hodges, H.G., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - I, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - J, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - J.W. Jackson, Cochran Farms, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Jenson-Salsbery Company, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - K, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Charles F. Kettering Foundation-"The Oxidation of Crytaline Carotene", 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Kent, L.C., 1949 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - L, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Ledlerle Laboratories, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - M, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Mc, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Mastitis Budget, 1948-1949 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Mastitis Control Program, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Mastitis Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Mastitis Reports, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Canton Regional Mastitis Lab, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Earlville Regional Mastitis Lab, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - East Aurora Regional Mastitis Lab, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Farmingdale Regional Mastitis Lab, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kingston Regional Mastitis Lab, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Methoxichlor Powder, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Moving the Vet. College, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Pitman-Moore Co., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Murphy, James M., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - N, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - O, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - P, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - R, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Ring, Lawrence A., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Schenley Laboratories Inc., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Schwardt, H.H., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Sharp & Dohme, Inc., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - E.R. Squibb & Sons, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Syracuse Pharmacal Co., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - T, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - U, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - University Policy Committee, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Upjohn Co., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - V, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Vassar Formula, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Veterinarians Wanted, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Vibrionic Abortion, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Vit-a-Bomb Company, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - W, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Wallace Laboratories, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - XYZ, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - 1949-1950
    - A, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Ambulatory Clinic-Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Ambulatory Clinic-Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Ambulatory Clinic, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 37)